WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
What's that?
I got a mysterious
package,
Postmarked Las Vegas.
Oh, "baume & mercier."
Oh my God.
This is so beautiful.
I had it engraved.
Here.
"You are my life.
Love, t."
They couldn't fit
"Tony."
I believe that.
Thank you.
But I don't know
what it's for.
Well, like I said,
I was sorry
I had to go out
to Vegas when I did.
Once you explained
You had to take care of
Christopher's business interests...
God knows
kelli'll need the money.
The baby.
I'm talking about
delay, right?
Just take care
of that, all right?
Bobby?
John stefano.
You touchin' asbestos?
No, I don't work
with that shit.
It's okay.
Shame about
Chris Moltisanti.
These bozos?
Ecuadorians.
Bunch of 'em polacks.
How come they ain't
wearing their space suits?
That's a union rule.
If I couldn't run this job
without that fucking contract,
Ain't none of us gonna
make any real scratch.
You don't got
an envelope?
You must have seen
fights before.
Your friends beating up
the African kid,
Why do you think that's
been impossible to shake?
They had my back after
all the shit with blanca.
You know, they care
about me.
Did you try to stop
the beating?
I'm one individual.
What could I do?
I mean, why can't I
catch a fuckin' break?
Your classes,
how are you enjoying those?
English is boring.
And the other one's
kind of interesting,
But it's pretty
depressing.
The israeli-Palestinian
conflict?
People blowing each other up
because their God says
They're allowed to live in a
certainatch of fuckin' sand.
Yeah, and other people's gods say
they're supposed to live there.
Maybe I shouldn't
have taken it.
You seem to be taking
it all personally.
These mujahideen assholes,
like in indonesia,
And they, like,
want to kill everybody.
Have you considered writing
about your experience
With the somali boy?
A short story, perhaps?
Why would I do that?
It might help
clarify your feelings.
I was watching cnn...
and this story about these
kids in some iraqi hospital,
How the burn unit doesn't have
the right medicine or something.
And then they show
this story
About some mall
in minnesota
And these gigantic
fat people
Buying stuff
And eating all
this shit.
You know, it's like
my parents.
I mean, you should
see our house.
I mean, the stupid
coffeemaker they got,
The media room.
Then there's blanca,
Her kid hardly talks.
She can't afford to send him
to a decent school.
You think your feelings
about blanca
In any way relate
to this African boy?
She's not black.
I mean,
She's pretty tan.
- Oh!
- There he is.
- Hey.
- Welcome back.
Welcome back, Ton'.
Good to see you again.
How was your trip?
Great.
Had a fuckin' blast.
Yeah?
Business too.
Christopher's shit.
Some fucking guys
out there owed him money.
Little Carmine took it on the
"cleaver" set. We had it framed.
Talk about a trip--
I met this girl,
she was fuckin' beautiful.
Oh yeah?
- Boys.
- Hey.
- We did peyote.
- Come on.
- Really?
- Bobby did mushrooms once.
Stuffed mushrooms,
a whole fuckin' platter.
Fuck you, huh?
Anyway, that's--
That's some nutty shit,
The desert...
the light.
I did "x" once. The
fucking was incredible.
Oh, yeah yeah, you kiddin'?
Off the fuckin' charts.
- You wouldn't believe it.
- Really?
And the sun...
came up...
oh yeah?
Well.
We saw stefano.
He didn't have
an envelope.
Any movement on that?
Eh, we should
probably see Phil.
I got dosed with acid once, back in '68.
I was with your dad
and them at the copa.
Fuckin' b.O.A.C stewardess
put it in my drink.
Jerry vale started
singing and I look over,
Your uncle jun's got laser
beams shooting out of his eyes.
I used to love
that house, but now...
it's so big,
especially at night.
You're afraid, you know,
all you got to do is call.
Right?
Two minutes,
I'll be over.
I know.
Thank you.
You've been so great.
Both of you.
Well, Meadow had another
mystery date.
That sounds exciting.
What are you doing?
Sit.
I made your favorite,
steak pizzaiol'.
You know they spray
a virus on beef
Rather than clean the ratshit
out of the slaughterhouses?
- What is this now?
- Jesus Christ.
It's true.
Read the paper.
I do
read the paper.
Never heard that.
I'm not talking
about the sports page.
I mean, the f.D.A.?
They approved a virus spray
Because it kills a similar
bacteria found on meat.
Must be
a good thing then.
Yeah.
For the meatpackers,
The fucking God
of the bottom line.
All right,
that's enough.
We're trying to eat here,
And you're upsetting people
that have been through a tragedy.
Fine. Bury your head
in the sand.
How about I bury yours
in that fuckin' wall instead?
- Tony.
- For 20 years, he won't crack a book,
All of a sudden he's the
world's foremost authority.
At least he's getting
an education.
An education's to help you
get a better job.
He's actually reading.
This can't be bad.
"The blood-Dimmed tide
is loosed,
And everywhere,
the ceremony of innocence
Is drowned;
The best lack
all conviction,
While the worst are full
of passionate intensity.
Surely some revelation
Is at hand."
"...Somewhere in the sands
of the desert
A shape with lion body
And the head of a man, a gaze
blank and pitiless as the sun,
Is moving its slow thighs,
While all about it reel shadows
of the indignant desert birds.
The darkness drops again;
But now I know that
twenty centuries of stony sleep
Were vexed to nightmare
by a rocking cradle,
And what rough beast,
its hour come round at last,
Slouches towards bethlehem
to be born?"
Hey, Tony.
You don't look
so good.
This job.
You want a sandwich?
A cannoli
On the house?
No, this microbe
of mine--
From Pakistan.
- Still?
- You got a minute?
We'd like to show you
some pictures.
Angelina Jolie,
I hope.
These the gentlemen?
That's them.
What the fuck?
What?
Don't know.
Financing, maybe.
- Maybe?
- Yeah.
Honestly, I'm not even sure we
still have them in the country.
Thanks
for stopping by.
Next time we'll have
party hats.
Hey.
Your nephew's widow,
She get my flowers?
Well, if you sent 'em,
I'm sure she did.
Well, I won't expect
a thank you anytime soon.
The grieving process, it takes
time the closer you are to somebody.
Yeah, I know.
So, brass tacks,
What brings you
all the way out to the city?
Good news. The condos
at the navy yard--
Paulie's guy at
the joint fitters
Says they're
breaking ground.
- Well, that is good.
- Good, yeah.
Uh, the other thing,
this asbestos--
I thought about
your offer.
What do you say
to 15%
Plus we forget
about the balance
Of what you owe me
on the vitamin truck?
First off,
it wasn't an offer.
It's my position: 25%.
That's it?
What else would you
like me to say?
Come on, Phil,
what's the problem?
I come here
in good faith,
I make a reasonable
counter.
Which I considered...
and rejected.
Do we need to talk
in private?
For what?
Okay then, in front
of everybody...
when you were sick
In the hospital,
We talked.
We shared a...
an understanding
about life.
This is business, Anthony.
Yeah, I know.
But I'm talking to you
here on a human level.
There's a limit, Phil.
Come on.
A point where business
bleeds into other shit,
Feelings make things
financially unfeasible.
Charles schwab
over here.
So that's it?
No leeway, no compromise,
just stupid fuckin' jokes?
You want compromise?
How's this?
20 years in the can,
I wanted manicott'.
I compromised.
I ate grilled cheese
off the radiator instead.
I wanted
to fuck a woman,
But I compromised.
I jacked off
in a tissue.
You see where
I'm going?
Yeah.
- Butch, coco, didn't anybody call you guys?
- About what?
- Don't tell me the fuckin' checks are late?
- There ain't any checks.
- The fuck you talkin' about?
- Silvio-- Mr. Soprano's guy--
Came by this morning,
said to pull your jobs.
- Whoa whoa whoa.
- Fuck that.
- Where's our money?
- I don't got it, there's no jobs.
Motherfucker.
I'm sorry, guys. Somebody
really should have called you.
Hey!
- Jesus Christ!
- Ho!
Guys, that's enough, come on.
It's not his fault.
- Oh, yeah? Maybe it's
your fuckin' fault?
Call the police!
Tony Soprano
owes you $320.
Hey.
I was just watching
"borat" on cable.
You can watch that thing 50
times and it's still hilarious.
He brings that lady
his shits.
It wasn't fair
to the people involved.
You loved it
when it came out.
What do you want,
Meadow?
- How was your exam?
- I didn't take it.
Leave that!
Okay?
Thank you.
Why didn't you
take the test?
'Cause I dropped out,
okay?
What's going on
with you?
I'm your sister,
You have
to talk to me.
Is this still
about blanca?
You know, I don't
know anymore.
I know how
you feel, okay?
When Finn and I split,
I cried every day
For, like, a month.
You realize we're
gonna bomb iran?
You don't know that.
You watch.
Bush, before he
leaves office--
And you know
I'm right.
Okay.
But you need to learn
to shut stuff out.
Are you crazy?
I mean, do you hear
what we're talking about?
You say that,
but I come in here
And you're surfing
the web for porn.
It's not porn.
"Al jazeera"?
Don't you ever feel like
there's no point to any of this?
Why don't you try
setting goals for yourself?
Maybe you
should move out?
Oh right,
in my condition?
I mean, I can't
hold a job.
Jesus, A.J., there has to
be something you can do.
Look, I'm ill, Meadow.
All right, I'm on medication.
Millions of people
take lexapro.
I need mom's cooking.
It could mess
with my blood chemistry.
Do mom and dad know
you dropped out?
No, and don't
tell them.
I took time off,
remember?
They broke my balls
but it really wasn't so bad.
Of course not.
I mean, you're their pet.
We're Italian, A.J.
You're their son.
Do you have any idea
what that means?
You'll always be
more important.
You're awake.
I made lincoln log
sandwiches.
Maybe later.
I am meeting gab
for lunch,
And then we are
stopping at nordstrom's.
If you go out, make sure
you set the alarm.
Okay?
Jeez!
Ah!
Somebody!
Help!
Help! My arms!
They're frozen!
A.J., what the fuck?
Dad! Help--!
Help!
No, dad!
Ah!
- My leg, it's stuck!
- On what?
Huh?
What the fuck
did you do?
Hel-- Help!
All right, I got you.
Stop fighting me.
- All right...
- Don't--
All right, turn around.
Grab the side.
Grab the side
right there.
All right.
God damn it.
Hold that.
Help me.
All right,
climb!
Ah!
What's wrong
with you?!
All right.
Are you all right?
All right, come here.
Come on.
Turn around.
Come on, baby.
You're all right, baby.
You're all right.
Well, here we are.
I'll get him settled. You can come
tomorrow during visiting hours.
I love you, sweetie.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
He's had a lot
of valium.
But he was better
for a while.
Look, it's not
your fault.
You warned us.
Come on, come on.
Come on,
it's gonna be okay.
It will, mom.
But he was always
so happy.
He was our
happy little boy.
I mean, God.
Come here, baby.
There you go.
White walls.
- Skip.
- Hey, Ton'.
There he is.
You hungry, t? You want, I'll
send the kid for baja fresh.
Anything from Phil?
No, not yet.
All right, let's dispense with the
500-Lb elephant in the room, eh?
My kid tried
to off himself.
We all fuckin' know.
That's it.
Nobody's got
nothing to say?
How's he doin', Ton'?
They got him
under observation.
Whatever the fuck
that means.
Stupid fuck.
Where did I lose
this kid?
What did I do wrong?
Whoa, come on.
Don't blame
yourself, t.
A lot of pressure
on kids today, Ton'.
Still, to try
to kill himself?
It's happens, skip.
Happen to your kids?
Or yours?
They're all
different, Ton'.
My son patrick?
I love him to death,
But he can be a moody prick sometimes.
Heather, you know,
she was 15,
She went through
a rough patch.
Jason, same thing.
And he's got the hyperactivity to boot.
My son too.
The older one, James.
- He tried to kill himself?
- No no.
I don't know, he--
He gets the blues.
The important thing is A.J.'S
getting the help he needs.
Whatever it is, I'm sure
it's a chemical imbalance.
Ask me, it's all these
toxins they're exposed to.
It fucks
with their brains.
Between the mercury
in fish alone,
It's a wonder there ain't
more kids jumping off bridges.
I can't
fuckin' shake it.
Shake what?
- I'm depressed.
- Excuse me?
I'm depressed.
I'm telling you,
don't you start now.
- What does that mean?
- It means what it means.
I have enough on my plate, I don't need
you adding to it with your bullshit.
Bullshit?
It's an illness.
And it's fuckin'
hereditary.
Thank you, I know.
I am intimately acquainted
with the Soprano curse.
Your father, your uncle,
your great-Grandfather
Who drove the donkey cart
off the road in avellino,
- All of it.
- What, you think it's a joke?
- Am I laughing?
- Then what are you saying?
He didn't get it
from my family,
That's all
I'm gonna say.
Your family don't
even talk.
Your father's
so bottled up
It's a wonder he's even
got a stomach left.
- As opposed to yours?
- At least my father was upfront about what was bothering him.
- Right, with a bullet through your mother's beehive hairdo.
- Oh, I knew it.
I was wondering how long it was gonna
take for you to throw that up at me.
You're amazing,
you know that?
In high school, you were
the happy-Go-Lucky rascal,
The comedian,
the rapscallion.
But all of that was bullshit, wasn't it?
Oh, poor you.
She got married
under false pretenses.
You've been playing
the depression card
Until it is worn
to shreds.
And now you've got
our son doing it.
Card? Card?
You heard me.
Oh, so it's
all me, huh?
Our Sonny boy? You had
nothing to do with it?
It wears you down, Tony.
That's all I'm saying.
Do you have any idea what it's
like to spend day after day
With somebody who is
constantly complaining?
Fuck you.
It could have been
a cry for help.
Aren't you listening?
He did cry for help.
He's lucky I came
home and heard him.
I meant
the botched attempt.
On some level,
he may have known
That the rope was too long
to keep him submerged.
Or he could just be
a fuckin' idiot.
Historically,
that's been the case.
Me and Carm were
getting along so good too.
My father and his
panic attacks,
My fuckin'
demented uncle,
Not to mention the other one--
Eckley the fuckin' retard.
You think there are other reasons
why your son is so unhappy?
He's got the world
by the balls--
Every fuckin' advantage--
And he hits one little pothole
and he goes into hysterics.
Yeah, I know.
I'm not taking
the rap,
Not completely.
She coddled him, his mother.
I said it before.
Every little problem,
she's right there
To pick him up
and wipe off his tears
On her apron strings.
Children need
to feel safe.
I'm sure that made him
into the man he is today.
Are you ashamed of him?
Yeah, actually I am.
The coward's way out.
Isn't that
what they call it?
I think whoever said that
didn't understand depression.
But you do, don't you?
Where's dad?
Oh, Meadow got rear-Ended
on bloomfield avenue.
- He'll come see you later.
- Is he still mad?
He was never mad, A.J.
He loves you.
How long do
I have to stay here?
Dr. Vogel thinks it
might be a good idea
For the time being
just to take a time-Out.
Like I'm in preschool?
Did you see
Dr. Vogel today?
Today we have group.
Did you eat today?
I had some turkey.
It had no flavor at all.
I'll bring some
chicken parm tomorrow.
I don't think
that's allowed
On account of all
the bulimic girls.
So it's front-Row mezzanine
at "grey gardens,"
- And the guy says--
- Excuse me?
- You're Tony Soprano's kid, right?
- Yeah.
Small world, running
into you like this, huh?
I'm sorry,
do I know you?
You got a little cream
on your mouth there, sweetie.
Be happy to add to it.
- What?
- Excuse me.
Lucky guy, her dad.
Must be fun tucking her
in at night, huh?
- Do you have a problem?
- Not yet.
Would you like one?
Coco, come on.
What?
I'm saying hello.
Come on,
let's go.
Hey, best to
your dad, huh?
What the hell
was that?
...but that is not
for you to decide.
Don't say anything.
What, are you two talking
about me again?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What?
Do you know a guy
named coco?
Why?
She was out
on a date last night
And he came over
and pulled some crap.
What?
How?
We were in the city,
little Italy.
We were
having dessert, and...
he came up
out of nowhere
And just started saying
all this weird stuff.
What kind of weird stuff?
How he'd like
to tuck me in at night.
Stuff like that.
- Tuck you in?
- I could smell the sambuca on his breath.
What exactly
did he say?
He came up to us
And he asked me if
I was your daughter
And then he said
I had whipped cream
On my mouth.
Yeah?
What else did he say?
It's all right.
It's okay.
He's an idiot,
But he's harmless.
I'll talk
to somebody.
So this boy
you're dating,
This man,
who is he?
You promise not to start
with an inquisition?
Will you stop with all
the secrecy, please?
- It's patrick Parisi, okay?
- You're kidding me?
That's exactly why I didn't
want to tell you guys,
And why he didn't tell
uncle Patsy.
I thought he--
Where are you going?
Meeting-- Sil.
We have vogel later,
don't forget.
I thought pat Parisi
was engaged.
They broke it off.
We kind of hooked up
at the "cleaver" premiere,
We started talking.
He's changed a lot.
I really like him.
So why the big mystery
all this time?
I knew you and daddy
never liked him.
No, it's not that
we didn't like him,
It's just...
so all those times
you told me
You were staying with your
friend kimmie in the city,
I suppose you were staying
at his apartment?
Sometimes.
Look, there's
something else.
What?
I've decided not
to go to med school.
What? Why?
Oh, it's just too hard.
- Isn't anything that's worthwhile?
- You have no idea.
- Of course not.
- Don't get sarcastic.
I really think
it's law for me.
I mean, you should hear patrick
talk about the justice system
And what it means.
It's really inspiring.
Obviously Sheila resents me.
I'm dating her father.
The sullen looks,
the transference to me
Of her issues
with her mom...
as your favorite
patient says,
"Maybe I should put
my shoe up her ass?"
Which patient of mine
says that?
Mine, Elliot.
Your favorite patient
of mine?
Oh.
He hasn't been
in the paper much lately.
You miss that,
don't you?
My father was a rabid
"untouchables" fan.
Make of that
what you will.
What, Elliot?
I ran into nancy duggan
last week.
- Do you know nancy?
- Vaguely.
She's on staff
at rikers island,
Works with a lot of
sociopaths, as you can imagine.
Anyway, she told me
something interesting.
A lot of studies
about talk therapy
As it relates
to sociopaths
And criminals,
One of them is the
criminal personality
Conducted by yochelson
at St. Elizabeth's.
Essentially
It concludes
That talk therapy,
While not only being
useless with sociopaths,
Actually serves
to validate them.
Yochelson says they sharpen
their skills as conmen
On their therapists.
Crocodile tears,
what have you.
Why are you smirking?
- I'm not.
- Oh really?
We showed data.
The one-Year
reconviction rates
Were higher for offenders in therapy
Than for those receiving
no treatment at all.
Uh, some peppers
and cheese.
Eh, gorgonzola,
all right? Don't forget.
Whoa whoa!
Sit down.
- Sit down.
- Easy easy.
You motherfucker.
My fucking daughter?
My fucking daughter,
you motherfucker.
My fuckin' daughter!
Hey, want some
sambuca with this?
Tony, you're making
a big fuckin' mistake here.
How about I put a bullet
in your fuckin' head, huh?
Don't do it!
You want some?
It's always what
you think, isn't it?
It's never how I feel.
Oh, poor you.
It's all your mother's
fault, isn't it?
- I didn't say that.
- You're a mama's boy.
You're gonna
call me names now?
No one is calling
anyone any names.
How about
my confirmation?
You called me
an animal.
I did not!
I was in the garage
and you said,
"What kind of animal smokes
marijuana at his confirmation?"
He was using illegal drugs
in the home.
Did it ever occur to you that I
might have been self-Medicating?
Give me a break,
will you?
And how about
second grade?
You made me show up to
school in that dorky raincoat.
I got beat up
because of it.
You would hole
up in that room for hours.
Because I was never really secure
expressing my feelings in that house.
I mean, that's why.
What kind of poem is that
to teach college students?
Would you like
to tell your parents
What your
grandmother said?
My mother?
Grandma--
Dad's mom.
What'd she say?
That it's all
a big nothing.
What is?
Life.
That was her,
all right.
Okay, fine, she said
those kinds of things--
She sat up in bed--
When she could
hardly move.
She could hardly
breathe.
She said in the end that your
friends and family let you down,
And that you die
in your own arms.
When was this?
When she was
in that nursing home
And you used
to make me go see her.
We're not too young
to be grandpas.
Ton'?
Carmine Lupertazzi.
- I'll see you later, skip.
- All right.
We should have dinner,
You know, Carm,
Donna, maybe the kids.
Yeah.
I hear wedding bells
are in the air.
You want anything?
No, I'm good.
If there's anything I can
do, Tony, for Anthony jr....
thank you.
When alexandra had
that bout of anorexia,
We had this terrific
psychologist.
She tried to kill herself,
your daughter?
No.
She had serious problems
though, didn't she?
Not really.
It's all under control.
So...
the reason I'm here
You could
probably guess.
What happened
at coco's restaurant.
This alteration
you had with him--
You're at
the precipice, Tony,
Of an enormous crossroad.
Phil's considering shutting
down the hackensack mall project
With a plumbing strike
as we speak.
Fuck it.
Let him.
Easy for you. I have
the scaffolding contract.
Oh, is that what
this is about, Carmine?
What do I owe you?
Come on, huh?
You know me better than that.
My daughter, Carmine.
My daughter.
You got a little girl.
You almost
killed the guy.
I should've killed him.
I'd have had total support,
- But I held myself back!
- You were being prudent.
Fuck that.
I lost it.
Timing couldn't have been
worse, but what the fuck?
So you go to Phil,
I go with you,
hats in hand,
Bended knees.
Why me, huh?
Doesn't every parent
make mistakes?
Why not you?
'Cause I'm
a good guy...
basically.
I love my family.
There's a balance.
There's a ying and a yang.
Huh?
You think you know.
You think you learned something.
Like when I got shot.
Know what?
All right.
When I was in Las Vegas,
I took peyote.
Curiosity,
I don't know.
You were searching
for something.
Well, I saw some things.
Not...
things, per se,
hallucinations,
Roger corman shit.
- It was kind of disappointing, there wasn't any of that.
- What was there?
It's kind of hard
to describe.
I mean, you've done it, right?
Acid, shit like that.
No.
All I can say is
I saw,
for pretty certain,
That this...
everything we see
and experience,
Is not all there is.
What else is there?
Something else.
But that's as far as
I'm gonna go with it.
I don't fuckin' know.
Alternate universes?
You gonna be
a fuckin' comedian now?
I'm not.
Maybe.
This is gonna
sound stupid...
but I saw at one point
that our mothers are...
they're bus drivers.
They're--
No, they are the bus.
See, they're the vehicle
that gets us here.
They drop us off
and go on their way.
They continue
on their journey.
And the problem is that we keep
trying to get back on the bus,
Instead of just
letting it go.
That's very insightful.
Jesus, don't act
so surprised.
You know...
you have these thoughts,
and you almost grab it.
And then...
pfft.
Butch, how are you?
Phil is not accepting
visitors right now.
I just talked to him
on the phone, butchie.
I just talked
to him in person.
He ain't seeing nobody.
What's going on, butch?
I just brokered
this thing.
He came here to make
a peace offering.
A semi-Trailer of drills--
Makitas.
We don't want
your fuckin' drills.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
That's right, cocksucker!
- Go back to new Jersey!
- Phil, what are you doin'?
Take that piece of shit
and get off my stoop.
But we just
talked about this.
Well, cooler heads
prevailed.
- Uncle philly!
- Uncle philly my ass.
Will you just come down
so we can discuss this?
There's nothing left
to discuss, Carmine.
I don't understand.
Why is he like this?
Hey, it's sleeping beauty.
I didn't sleep a wink.
I know, we've been
waiting for you.
We have the chess set
all ready.
- He cheats.
- Hello, honest abe?
- Whatever.
- We just haven't played for so long.
I know, I just got
all this stress at work.
It's cool, it happens
to a lot of people.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
More than half of adults
report experiencing
Some kind of insomnia at
least a few nights a week.
We just
want you back.
- Thanks, guys.
- When you can't sleep...
no food in
the unit, sir.